{
	"questions": [
		{
			"question_text": "Ladaka",
			"question_speech": "लड़का",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Boy",
				"Girl"
			],
			"answer": "Boy",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Ladakay",
			"question_speech": "लड़के",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Boys",
				"Girls"
			],
			"answer": "Boys",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Ladaki",
			"question_speech": "लड़की",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Boy",
				"Girl"
			],
			"answer": "Girl",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Ladakiyaan",
			"question_speech": "लड़कियाँ",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Boys",
				"Girls"
			],
			"answer": "Girls",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Aadmi",
			"question_speech": "आदमी",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Man",
				"Woman"
			],
			"answer": "Man",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Aurat",
			"question_speech": "औरत",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Man",
				"Woman"
			],
			"answer": "Woman",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Paani",
			"question_speech": "पानी",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Milk",
				"Water"
			],
			"answer": "Water",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Doodh",
			"question_speech": "दूध",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Milk",
				"Water"
			],
			"answer": "Milk",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Peena",
			"question_speech": "पीना",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Eat",
				"Drink"
			],
			"answer": "Drink",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Khaana",
			"question_speech": "खाना",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Food",
				"Drink"
			],
			"answer": "Food",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Chaaval",
			"question_speech": "चावल",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Bread",
				"Rice"
			],
			"answer": "Rice",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Anda",
			"question_speech": "अंडा",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Bread",
				"Egg"
			],
			"answer": "Egg",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Sabzi",
			"question_speech": "सब्ज़ी",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Fruit",
				"Vegetable"
			],
			"answer": "Vegetable",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Sabziyaan",
			"question_speech": "सब्ज़ियां",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Fruits",
				"Vegetables"
			],
			"answer": "Vegetables",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Fal",
			"question_speech": "फल",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Fruit",
				"Vegetable"
			],
			"answer": "Fruit",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Kapada",
			"question_speech": "कपड़ा",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Cloth",
				"Shoe"
			],
			"answer": "Cloth",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Kapade",
			"question_speech": "कपड़े",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Clothes",
				"Shoes"
			],
			"answer": "Clothes",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Joota",
			"question_speech": "जूता",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Cloth",
				"Shoe"
			],
			"answer": "Shoe",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Jootay",
			"question_speech": "जूते",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Clothes",
				"Shoes"
			],
			"answer": "Shoes",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Haath",
			"question_speech": "हाथ",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Hand",
				"Leg"
			],
			"answer": "Hand",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Paer",
			"question_speech": "पैर",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Hand",
				"Leg"
			],
			"answer": "Leg",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Din",
			"question_speech": "दिन",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Day",
				"Night"
			],
			"answer": "Day",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Raat",
			"question_speech": "रात",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Day",
				"Night"
			],
			"answer": "Night",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Subah",
			"question_speech": "सुबह",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Morning",
				"Evening"
			],
			"answer": "Morning",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Shaam",
			"question_speech": "शाम",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Morning",
				"Evening"
			],
			"answer": "Evening",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Garam",
			"question_speech": "गरम",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Hot",
				"Cold"
			],
			"answer": "Hot",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Thanda",
			"question_speech": "ठंडा",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Hot",
				"Cold"
			],
			"answer": "Cold",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Garmee",
			"question_speech": "गर्मी",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Heat",
				"Cold"
			],
			"answer": "Heat",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Haan",
			"question_speech": "हां",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Yes",
				"No"
			],
			"answer": "Yes",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Nahin",
			"question_speech": "नहीं",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Yes",
				"No"
			],
			"answer": "No",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Achchha",
			"question_speech": "अच्छा",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Good",
				"Bad"
			],
			"answer": "Good",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Ganda",
			"question_speech": "गंदा",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Good",
				"Bad"
			],
			"answer": "Bad",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Saaf",
			"question_speech": "साफ़",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Dirty",
				"Clean"
			],
			"answer": "Clean",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Ganda",
			"question_speech": "गंदा",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Dirty",
				"Clean"
			],
			"answer": "Dirty",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Naya",
			"question_speech": "नया",
			"answer_choices": [
				"New",
				"Old"
			],
			"answer": "New",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Puraana",
			"question_speech": "पुराना",
			"answer_choices": [
				"New",
				"Old"
			],
			"answer": "Old",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Andar",
			"question_speech": "अंदर",
			"answer_choices": [
				"In",
				"Out"
			],
			"answer": "In",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Baahar",
			"question_speech": "बाहर",
			"answer_choices": [
				"In",
				"Out"
			],
			"answer": "Out",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Oopar",
			"question_speech": "ऊपर",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Up",
				"Down"
			],
			"answer": "Up",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Neeche",
			"question_speech": "नीचे",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Up",
				"Down"
			],
			"answer": "Down",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Pasand",
			"question_speech": "पसंद",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Like",
				"Don't Like"
			],
			"answer": "Like",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Nahin Pasand",
			"question_speech": "नहीं पसंद",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Like",
				"Don't Like"
			],
			"answer": "Don't Like",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Main",
			"question_speech": "मैं",
			"answer_choices": [
				"You",
				"I"
			],
			"answer": "I",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Aap",
			"question_speech": "आप",
			"answer_choices": [
				"You",
				"I"
			],
			"answer": "You",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Tum",
			"question_speech": "तुम",
			"answer_choices": [
				"You",
				"I"
			],
			"answer": "You",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Hum",
			"question_speech": "हम",
			"answer_choices": [
				"We",
				"They"
			],
			"answer": "We",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Vo",
			"question_speech": "वो",
			"answer_choices": [
				"He",
				"Me"
			],
			"answer": "He",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Vo",
			"question_speech": "वो",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Me",
				"She"
			],
			"answer": "She",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Mera",
			"question_speech": "मेरा",
			"answer_choices": [
				"My",
				"Your"
			],
			"answer": "My",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Aapka",
			"question_speech": "आपका",
			"answer_choices": [
				"My",
				"Your"
			],
			"answer": "Your",
			"include": "sometimes"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Ghar",
			"question_speech": "घर",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Home",
				"School"
			],
			"answer": "Home",
			"include": "always"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Bhai",
			"question_speech": "भाई",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Brother",
				"Sister"
			],
			"answer": "Brother",
			"include": "always"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Bahan",
			"question_speech": "बहन",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Brother",
				"Sister"
			],
			"answer": "Sister",
			"include": "always"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Dost",
			"question_speech": "दोस्त",
			"answer_choices": [
				"Friend",
				"Sister"
			],
			"answer": "Friend",
			"include": "always"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Aap kaise ho?",
			"question_speech": "आप कैसे हो?",
			"answer_choices": [
				"How are you?",
				"Who am I?"
			],
			"answer": "How are you?",
			"include": "always"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Main theek hoon",
			"question_speech": "मैं ठीक हूँ",
			"answer_choices": [
				"I am fine",
				"You are sad"
			],
			"answer": "I am fine",
			"include": "always"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Main game khel rahi hoon",
			"question_speech": "में गेम खेल रही हूँ",
			"answer_choices": [
				"I am playing a game",
				"I am eating ice-cream"
			],
			"answer": "I am playing a game",
			"include": "always"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Main ice-cream kha rahi hoon",
			"question_speech": "मैं ice-cream खा रहीं हूँ",
			"answer_choices": [
				"I am playing a game",
				"I am eating ice-cream"
			],
			"answer": "I am eating ice-cream",
			"include": "always"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Main dekh rahi hoon",
			"question_speech": "मैं देख रही हूं",
			"answer_choices": [
				"I am watching",
				"I am reading"
			],
			"answer": "I am watching",
			"include": "always"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "Main pad rahi hoon",
			"question_speech": "मैं पढ़ रही हूं",
			"answer_choices": [
				"I am watching",
				"I am reading"
			],
			"answer": "I am reading",
			"include": "always"
		}
	]
}